https://www.kegerators.com/privacy/

Kegerators.com Privacy Policy
Kegerators.com is an internet entity which functions as a bridge between
potential kegerator and draft beer equipment buyers and various kegerator and draft beer equipment providers. We
consider privacy to be an extremely important issue. We are committed to
protecting your privacy and to delivering content and technology that gives you
the most powerful and secure online experience. We are also committed to a high ethic standard when doing our online business. Below is an outline of our Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for Kegerators.com. The purpose
of this Privacy Policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor to Kegerators.com,
what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit the site, how
we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices
you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information.
First, like most regular business sites on the Internet, we collect traffic
data. Each time a visitor comes to our web site our servers collect basic
technical information including visitor's domain name, referral data, and
browser and platform type. This information is analyzed in aggregate, and we
never track specific sessions and paths people take on the web site. Traffic
information is only given out on a need to know basis and is at times shared
with advertisers.
Second, unlike most regular business sites on the internet, during the process
of buying draft beer equipment off of our site, Kegerators.com does not collect or
store any personal data, such as a visitor's name, address, date of birth, phone
number, e-mail address, social security number, because it contains direct links
to on-line providers for all featured draft beer equipment.
All kegerator and draft beer equipment purchases with personal data are directly taken and stored on the
providers' web servers.
With respect to security: the providers always use industry-standard
encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged.
×
Instant BEER MEISTER® Coupon
$25 OFF
Sign up for our deal alerts and INSTANTLY receive a $25 off coupon.
Sign Up Today!
Subscribe and save. Offer Expires 12/11/20
